Summary

Junior Web Developer specializing in backend development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects.

Having completed a course in Node.js, hadeel has a solid understanding of basic concepts, including asynchronous programming, and the Node.js runtime environment. she has gained experience dealing with database operations(MongoDB) and API, implementing server-side logic using popular frameworks such as Express.js.

Skills

- JavaScript
- Express.js
- APIs: Understand how to handle HTTP methods, and work with JSON data.
- Router

- Databases (MongoDB)
- basic understanding of HTML5, CSS3, and Bootstrap.
- React JS ,Formik and Yup
- Redux toolkit and HOC.

Experience

Training of Node js 02/2023 to 05/2023 remotely

- Understanding Events, Callbacks, and Promises.
- Creating APIs and handling JSON data.
- Connecting to databases (MongoDB).
- Building server-side applications with Node.js and libraries (Express.js).
- I'm doing a Dashboard project using monodb and express.

Traning of React js 10/2022 to 2/2023 remotely

- Training for Component (Function, Class).
- Training for Props, state.
- Training for Component Life cycle.
- Training for Handling Events.
- Training for Controlled components.
- Training for Validation using Yup.
- Training for React router and React router dom.
- Training for Integration with APIs using Axios.
- Training for Hooks, Fragments.

• I'm doing a Portfolio Project.

Traning of React js 11/2022 to 2/2023 Geeks

Gaza Sky

- Components and Props: Understanding how to create and use components in React and pass props (properties) to those components.
- Interactivity and State: Learning how to manage state in React applications and how components respond to user events and interactions. (Redux)
- Navigation and Routing: Organizing application navigation and creating a routing system using React Router library.
- Data Fetching: Fetching data from external sources using APIs and libraries like axios or Fetch.
- Working with Forms: Creating and handling forms, and dealing with user inputs in React applications.

Education

Bachelor of Science: Information Technology

Al-Aqsa University

Certifications

React JS: Gaza sky Geeks, online diploma of React js.

Node JS: **online diploma of Node js**. Programming Languages: **JavaScript.**